Search

Get more than news. Get insights.

Subscribe

Subscribe

Privacy Policy
==============

**Updated** October 12, 2023

The Daily Upside, LLC. (“we” or “us” or “our”) respects the privacy of our users (“user” or “you”). This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use and disclose your information when you visit our website www.thedailyupside.com, mobile website, social media channels and subscribe to our newsletter (collectively, the “Site”). Please read this privacy policy carefully.  If you do not accept the terms as described in the Privacy Policy, do not access the site.

User Consent
------------

When you disclose any of your Personal Data (as defined below, “Personal Data”) through our Site, you are agreeing to the terms as described in this Privacy Policy and expressly consent to the use of your Personal Data as described herein.

Collection of Your Information
------------------------------

We may collect information about you in a number of ways. The information we may collect on the Site includes:

1. **Personal Data**  
    Personal Data includes identifiable information such as your name and email address. In no way are you obligated to provide us with Personal Data of any kind.  However, your refusal to do so may prevent you from accessing certain features of the site and receiving the Newsletter.
2. **Information Collected Automatically**  
    Our websites automatically collects information such as your IP address, browser type, and time spent on the various pages in our Site.  If you are using your mobile phone, this information may also include your device type, model, manufacturer and location.  This information is not personalized, and is not connected to the Personal Data that you choose to share with us.
3. **Data From Contests, Giveaways, and Surveys**  
    As part of contests and giveaways, we may collect other information from you including your shipping address and full name.

Use of Your Information
-----------------------

The primary reason we collect your personal information, including your email address, is for the sole purpose of sending you The Daily Upside newsletter (the “Newsletter”).   The other reasons we collect your personal information are to:

* Improve the efficiency and operation of the Site.
* Monitor Site usage and improve user experience.
* Respond to product and customer service requests.

Disclosure of Your Information
------------------------------

We may disclose the personal information we collect about you to a third party for certain, limited business purposes including (but not limited to) improving the quality of our offering.

**Third-Party Service Providers**  
We may share information with third parties to assist us with email delivery optimization or marketing assistance.

**Other Third Parties**  
We may share annonymized information with advertisers for the sole purpose of conducting general business analysis.  We may also share your annonymized information for the purpose of marketing analysis.

Tracking Technologies
---------------------

**Cookies**  
To learn more about how we use these and your choices in relation to these tracking technologies, please refer to our [Cookie Policy.](https://www.thedailyupside.com/cookie-policy/)

**Website Analytics**  
We may also use services such as Google Analytics to allow tracking technologies to analyze usage of the Site and determine the popularity of certain content. By accessing our Site, you expressly consent to the use of your information by these third-party services.

**Third-Party Websites:**  
The Site may contain links to third-party websites including advertisements and services not affiliated with us.  Once you have used these links to leave the Site, we cannot guarantee the privacy of your information.  Before visiting any third-party sites, you should carefully review their privacy policies.  We are not responsible for the content, privacy or security of any third-party site.

**Google Products**:  
The Site may use services from Google including Google Analytics and Google Ads, please review [How Google Uses This Information.](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites)

Policy for Children
-------------------

The privacy of children is extremely important to us.  The use of our Site and Newsletter is not intended for children.  We do not knowingly collect Personal Data from children, nor do we intentionally market to children.

Opt-Out Feature
---------------

You have the option to stop receiving newsletters and your option.  At the bottom of each of our emails, simply click the “Unsubscribe” link, and we will discontinue sending you the Newsletter.  You can also email us your opt-out request at: [squad@thedailyupside.com](mailto:squad@thedailyupside.com).  At your request, we will remove any of your personal from our databases.

Terms of Service (Last Updated October 12, 2023)

Indemnity and Hold Harmless
---------------------------

The newsletters published by The Daily Upside, LLC are for informational purposes only, are not intended to serve as a recommendation to buy or sell any security and are not an offer or sale of a security.  They are also not research reports and are not intended to serve as the basis for any investment decision.  Any third-party views reflected herein do not reflect the opinion of The Daily Upside, LLC.  All investments involve risk and the past performance of a security does not guarantee future results or returns. There is always the potential for financial loss when investing in securities or other financial products. Investors should consider their investment objectives and risks before investing.  
To the maximum extent permitted by law, you agree to indemnify and hold harmless The Daily Upside, LLC, its affiliates, managers, shareholders and employees from all claims, including reasonable attorneys’ fees, arising out of or in relation to the terms outlined in this Privacy Policy and Terms of Service.

Disclaimer of Warranties and Limitation of Liability
----------------------------------------------------

Your access of our Site is at your sole risk.  If you are dissatisfied with any of the content on our Site or with any of the terms described herein, your sole remedy is to discontinue accessing our Site and Newsletter.  The Daily Upside does not warrant that the services will be uninterrupted or error-free.  We disclaim any responsibility for the accuracy or reliability of the content contained within the Site.  Nothing in our Newsletter is intended to be financial advice, and we advice you contact a registered financial advisor before making any investment decision.

The Daily Upside, LLC, its directors, officers, managers, employees and its shareholders are not liable for damages of any kind.

Contact Us
----------

If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or Terms of Service, please contact us at:

The Daily Upside, LLC.

© 2024 The Daily Upside

###### Subscribe to Delivering razor sharp analysis and perspective on all things finance, economics, and markets.

Subscribe
